# JASON SILVIA

Technical and creative professional with 10 years experience and a passion for content creation and curation. Seeking to leverage experience in content consulting, solutions design, and training in the fields of content creation and production.

in linkedin.com/in/jasonsilvia/

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Audio Engineer/Music Producer/DJ/Content Creator, Freelance

Providence, RI • Dec 2020 - Present

- · Provided music & audio production services for musicians and small business clients
- Served as DJ to venues (New Harvest, Trinity Beer Garden) and live event consultant
- · Provided creative content consulting services for musicians, and small businesses

## **Specialty Content Consultant, Dell Technologies**

Hopkinton, MA • Nov 2019 - Dec 2020

- Analyzed, curated, and created training for Unstructured Data and Data Protection presales orgs
- Collaborated with education, business leadership, engineering, marketing, and operations teams
- Advised business leadership on the creation of new/updated presales training content
- · Created and managed training courses for in-person & virtual new hire onboarding

#### Solutions Architect, Dell Technologies

Franklin, MA • June 2017 - November 2019

- Developed and proposed fully integrated technology solutions: servers, storage, & networking
- Acted as technical expert and consultant for all presales activities
- Performed analysis of customer business and technical objectives
- Created and developed technical aspects and documentation of sales campaigns
- · Conducted customer facing campaigns, training, and demos
- Training instructor for the XtremIO product line

# **Technical Service Engineer, Dell Technologies**

Hopkinton, MA • March 2015 — June 2017

- Provided technical support expertise for XtremIO all flash storage array
- · Created both internal and customer facing documentation/processes to resolve customer issues

#### **Retention Marketing Specialist Email, Schneider Electric**

West Kingston, RI • June 2012 — December 2013

- · Design, production, and management of email campaigns for North America and global orgs
- Reintroduced e-commerce email marketing program for APC by Schneider Electric brand
- · Introduced, deployed, and administered Litmus email marketing analytics tool company wide

#### SKILLS

**Audio Engineering** 

DJ Pro Tools

Music & Podcast Production

Content Creation & Management

Project Management

Technical Solution
Design

Image & Video Editing

Copywriting

## **EDUCATION**

# New England Institute of Technology

East Greenwich, RI 2008 – 2011

Bachelor of Science - IT Networking

## **Full Sail University**

Winter Park, FL 2004 – 2005

Associate of Arts -Recording Arts Technology